summerinfant.com 2018-10-05

# Summer Infant - Baby Products

Summer Infant values our relationship with every customer and respects any personal information entrusted to us. Accordingly, we have spelled out the following privacy statement with you in mind. This privacy policy sets out how Summer Infant, Inc. uses and protects any personal information that you give Summer Infant when you use this website; Summer Infant is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.  Summer Infant may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from October 1, 2010.

  **What we collect**  
We may collect the following information: name and/or baby(s) name, contact information including email address, demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests and other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.   If you subscribe for a service for which we charge a recurring fee, we may also collect the password for your account and your credit card information.

  What we do with the information we gather? We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better products.  We may also monitor your content to make sure you are complying with our Acceptable Use Policy.  Here are some other ways we may use your information:

-Internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and customer service. We may periodically send promotional email or social media postings about new products, special offers from Summer Infant or one of our retailers, contests, or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. If you subscribe to a fee-bearing service, we may use the information to collect the fees that we charge and to limit access to your account to those whom you authorize to use it.

-Market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail to conduct market research.  We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. We may provide your information to our third party partners for marketing or promotional purposes. We will never sell your information. 

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

  **How we use cookies**  
A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

  Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

  Links to other websites: Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

  **Controlling your personal information**  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.  If there is no box, or if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes and no longer want us to do so, you may change your preference at any time by writing to or emailing us at [info@summerinfant.com](mailto:info@summerinfant.com).

  We do not sell, or lease your personal information to third parties. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties that we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information that we hold about you and request that we make corrections to any inaccuracies in our records that pertain to your personal information.

  If you wish to obtain a copy of the personal information about you that is in our possession, please write to or email us at: [customerservice@summerinfant.com](mailto:customerservice@summerinfant.com)

  Summer Infant Consumer Relations Department  
1275 Park East Drive  
Woonsocket, Rhode Island 02895
